You don't assign him. You unleash him.
The Soldier is a action, drama film directed by James Glickenhaus.
Terrorists take over a plutonium bomb and threaten to
detonate it in a Saudi Arabian oil field.
A special anti-terrorist unit is sent in to stop them.
The Soldier, played by Ken Wahl.
Susan Goodman, played by Alberta Watson.
Ivan, played by Jeremiah Sullivan.
The President, played by William Prince.
The Soldier's Force, played by Joaquim de Almeida.
Soldier's Force, played by Peter Hooten.
The Soldier (also released as Codename: The Soldier) is a 1982 American Cold War action-thriller film written, directed, and produced by James Glickenhaus The film
stars Ken Wahl, Alberta Watson, William Prince, Joaquim de Almeida, and Klaus Kinski, that featured a cameo by rising country superstar George Strait.
The film was shot on location in Philadelphia, Buffalo and New
York City, New York, West Berlin, and Israel.
The ski sequence was filmed in St Anton am Arlberg in Austria.
The original score was composed and performed by the
German electronic band Tangerine Dream.
The film explores themes of central intelligence agency (cia), oil, terrorism.
The tone is emotional.